gameculture.com 2011-11-01

# PRIVACY POLICY | Entertainment Consumers Association (ECA)

**ECA PRIVACY POLICY**

The ECA respects the privacy of our members and users of our website. We realize that you care about how your personal information is used and shared. This privacy policy discloses how we collect, use, and share information gathered about you on our web site.

We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by Entertainment Consumers Association, ("ECA"). (The ECA Network includes all Web sites and certain other Internet media properties hyper linked from the ECA Media corporate Web site.) The following discloses our Privacy Policy.

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**  
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" or IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the ECA Network, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site.

Our Web servers also collect information about the type of Internet browser you are using, operating system, as well as which of ECA's Web pages you have accessed. This information is used to help our team develop Web sites to display properly for the majority of our visitors.

Our Web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors.

**Does ECA use cookies?**  
_Yes, ECA uses cookies_. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are often used to provide you with a customized experience. At no time is any personal information stored within one of our cookies.

Accepting cookies through your browser is a personal choice. You can sill enjoy ECA's Web sites if you choose not to accept cookies.

**What information do you collect when I complete the "Contact Us" form?**  
Any information supplied through our contact forms is used to aid our business to respond to your request and provide you with the necessary information.

_Your email address may be entered to receive ECA's electronic newsletter. You can un-subscribe to this Newsletter at any time._

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**  
ECA will not sell or otherwise provide the information we collect to outside third parties for the purpose of direct or indirect mass email marketing.

ECA will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when such information is for a member who gained their membership via underwriting from one of our sponsors. In such case, we will only share that member’s information with that particular partner. ECA will also disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

1.    Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ECA; 

2.    Protect and defend the rights or property of the ECA Network of sites and related properties, or visitors to the ECA Network of sites and related properties; 

3.    Identify persons who may be violating the law, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the ECA Network or its related properties, 

**What safeguards are in place?**  
ECA is obligated to protect your personal information by making reasonable security arrangements against such risks as unauthorized access, use, collection, disclosure or disposal. Security measures have been integrated into the design, implementation and day-to-day operating practices as part of ECA's commitment to protect the personal information it holds.

**What else should I know about my privacy when online?**  
The ECA Network contains many hyperlinks to third party Web sites. ECA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party Web sites or advertisers. ECA does not share any of the individual personal information you provide ECA with the third parties to which ECA links, except as outlined above regarding underwritten memberships. Please check with those Web sites to determine their privacy policies.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

**Consent To This Agreement**  
By using the ECA Network, you consent to the collection and use of information by ECA as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Please send any questions about ECA's Privacy Policy to:

email: [feedback@theeca.com](mailto:feedback@theeca.com "mailto:feedback@theeca.com")  
phone: +1 (203) 761-6180
